let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: " How do you make important decisions?",
        answer: "A. I am more likely to use my head and hard facts over my heart.",
        options: [
            "A. I am more likely to use my head and hard facts over my heart.",
            "B. I go with my gut because it is important to trust myself!"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: " You have the option to take a statistics or a photography class. Which one will you pick?",
        answer: "B. Statistics, no contest.",
        options: [
            "A. Most likely photography.",
            "B. Statistics, no contest."
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: " You have a bunch of project works that need doing- how do you tackle them?",
        answer: "A. Methodically, I organize them by importance and finish them one by one.",
        options: [
            "A. Methodically, I organize them by importance and finish them one by one.",
            "B. I prioritize them by how interesting they are to me and complete them one by one."
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: " Your workspace is super messy. How do you deal with that?",
        answer: "B. It's definitely not ideal, I organize everything as soon as possible.",
        options: [
            "A. I don't mind clutter, but I try rearranging it so it's atleast easier to find stuff.",
            "B. It's definitely not ideal, I organize everything as soon as possible."
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: " Do you ever struggle with consistency?",
        answer: "A. I like to stick to a tight schedule.",
        options: [
            "A. I like to stick to a tight schedule.",
            "B. Routine is boring, so I like to go with the flow."
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: " As a child, how well did you follow rules?",
        answer: "B. I was super well-behaved.",
        options: [
            "A. I tried to be respectful, but I definitely questioned a lot of rules.",
            "B. I was super well-behaved."
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: " You are getting a haircut. What's the easiest way to tell the barber what hairstyle you want?",
        answer: "B. I offer the most important details and let the barber fill in the rest.",
        options: [
            "A. I create a collage of hairstyle photos that I can share with my hair stylist.",
            "B. I offer the most important details and let the barber fill in the rest."
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: " How often do you catch yourself daydreaming?",
        answer: "A. I daydream from time to time, but I wouldn't say it's a habit.",
        options: [
            "A. I daydream from time to time, but I wouldn't say it's a habit.",
            "B. All the time. I have a pretty strong imagination."
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: " Your birthday is coming up. How do you plan it?",
        answer: "B. I plan it down to the tiniest details.",
        options: [
            "A. I prefer having fun in the moment.",
            "B. I plan it down to the tiniest details."
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: " You have to share a story- what's your storytelling style?",
        answer: "B. I will give a summary but add a few of the most interesting details.",
        options: [
            "A. I tell every detail of the story with perfect accuracy.",
            "B. I will give a summary but add a few of the most interesting details."
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: " What does your closet look like right now?",
        answer: "B. Every type of clothing has its own spot and stays carefully folded.",
        options: [
            "A. I keep all my clothing in a spot but don't really have the time to fold or organize.",
            "B. Every type of clothing has its own spot and stays carefully folded."
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: " When you meet someone new, what do you remember best?",
        answer: "A. I remember their names and important details but don't really recall faces.",
        options: [
            "A. I remember their names and important details but don't really recall faces.",
            "B. I am better with faces than with names, but sometimes I can connect the dots." 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: " When you hear a new song, what would you usually do?",
        answer: "B. Check up the lyrics of the song first.",
        options: [
            "A. Listen to the melody and rhythm first",
            "B. Check up the lyrics of the song first."
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: " When you are meeting someone, you typically: ",
        answer: "A. Show up early, just in case.",
        options: [
            "A. Show up early, just in case.",
            "B. Arrive on time or slightly later."
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: " When reading a book or an article: ",
        answer: "A. I pay attention to every word and every detail.",
        options: [
            "A. I pay attention to every word and every detail.",
            "B. I prefer to skim through and focus on the most interesting parts."
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: " If you were to cook right now, you would rather: ",
        answer: "B. Follow a recipe step by step.",
        options:[
            "A. Not use a recipe and just freestyle it to create something new.",
            "B. Follow a recipe step by step."
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: " When you watch a movie, you pay more attention to:",
        answer: "A. The storyline.",
        options: [
            "A. The storyline.",
            "B. The acting"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: " While working on math problems, you run into one that you have done before and you had gotten it right the first time around. With plenty of time to work on the problem, you would:",
        answer: "B. Solve the problem the way you had solved it the first time.",
        options: [
            "A. Try to solve the problem using a different approach.",
            "B. Solve the problem the way you had solved it the first time."
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: " When it comes to math problems, you are better at:",
        answer: "A. Straight forward number calculations.",
        options: [
            "A. Straight forward number calculations.",
            "B. Problems involving shapes."
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: " If you were to learn something new, you would choose to learn:",
        answer: "B. A new language",
        options: [
            "A. A new art form such as drawing or dancing.",
            "B. A new language"
        ]
    }
]


